{
    "subject": "resource/Carl_Stumpf",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Franz_Brentano",
    "human_readable": "Carl Stumpf was influenced by Franz Brentano.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9459317326545715,
            "question": "In what way was Carl Stumpf connected to Franz Brentano?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9437576532363892,
            "question": "Did Franz Brentano's work have an impact on Carl Stumpf's thinking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9429481029510498,
            "question": "Who influenced Carl Stumpf?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.931433379650116,
            "question": "What can we learn about Carl Stumpf's philosophical influences from his connection to Franz Brentano?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9034652709960938,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Carl Stumpf and Franz Brentano?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9031075835227966,
            "question": "Was Franz Brentano a mentor to Carl Stumpf?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8536931872367859,
            "question": "What philosophical ideas might Carl Stumpf have learned from Franz Brentano?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7988715171813965,
            "question": "How did the work of Franz Brentano shape Carl Stumpf's approach to philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7938722372055054,
            "question": "Can you name philosophers who influenced Carl Stumpf?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7236481308937073,
            "question": "Who was a notable figure in philosophy that impacted Carl Stumpf's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carl Stumpf was influenced by Franz Brentano.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5169_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name philosophers who influenced Carl Stumpf?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5169_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the work of Franz Brentano shape Carl Stumpf's approach to philosophy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5169_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What philosophical ideas might Carl Stumpf have learned from Franz Brentano?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5169_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5169_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Specifically, multiple files mention that Carl Stumpf studied with Franz Brentano at the University of W\u00fcrzburg (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5169/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt) and that he was influenced by Brentano's philosophical ideas correlating to psychology, intentional mental acts, and consciousness (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5169/re-ranker-msmarco/17.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Carl Stumpf was influenced by Franz Brentano.\" Specifically, the documents mention that Carl Stumpf studied with Franz Brentano at the University of W\u00fcrzburg and that his education under Brentano significantly contributed to his own work in psychology and philosophy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}